

Peltolankatu 5 E, 80220 Joensuu

(+358) 465 823 714

 \sim

hpham@uef.fi

hogan-pham.com

github.com/HoganHPH

OBJECTIVE

With 3 years of experience in Artificial Intelligence and passion for Web Development, I am dedicated to advancing my expertise through research and practical applications. Currently pursuing an IT Master's degree at University of Eastern Finland, I aspire to contribute my skills and knowledge to real-world social impact projects.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Chief skills: Artificial Intelligence, Web Development

Frameworks:

- ❖ Al engineering: Pytorch, Scikit-learn, NLTK, Hugging Face, LangChain
- Webapp deployment: FastAPI, Flask, React.js
- * Database: MySQL, MongoDB
- Source management: Git, Docker
- Cloud service: AWS

WORK EXPERIENCE

Al Researcher Jan 2023 - Dec 2023 Hanoi, Vietnam

Information Technology Center, Thuy Loi University

- Project: Content-Based Image Retrieval (CBIR)
 - Technologies: Pytorch Geometric
 - Description: Investigating graph-based AI solutions for image search engines, conducting experiments and writing research papers.

Al Engineer June 2022 - Dec 2022 Hanoi, Vietnam

Akabot, FPT Corporation

- Project: Electrical Invoice Information Extraction
- Technologies: YOLOv7, DBNet, MMOCR, FastAPI, Docker
- Description: Building AI solutions for document information extraction. Integrating AI model into backend api modules for further deployment.

Feb 2021 - May 2022 Al Researcher (Intern) Hanoi, Vietnam Laboratory x Naver AI Center, Post and Telecommunication Institute of Technology

Technologies: Python, Pytorch

Description: Building AI model solving computer-vision related laboratory projects.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

Master of Science in Information Technology | University of Eastern Finland - In Progress Awarded a 2-year scholarship of 50%

Degree of Engineer in Information Technology | Post and Telecommunications Institute of Technology

Minor: Software Engineering

Assessment: Very Good – GPA 3.27/4. (Ranked in the top 7% of graduating students)

Python and Machine Learning Specialization | FPT Software Academy

o Received a training scholarship in Python and Machine Learning

Sep 2018 - April 2023 Hanoi, Vietnam

Sep 2024 – Present

Joensuu, Finland

Jan 2021 - May 2021 Hanoi, Vietnam

PUBLICATIONS

Conference Papers

Hoang, P.H., Thanh, N.V., & Quynh, N.H. (2023). Image Representation Learning with Graph Convolutional Network for Content-Based Image Retrieval. Proceedings of the National Conference on Fundamental and Applied IT Research (FAIR 2023), Da Nang City, Vietnam, September 28-29, 2023. DOI: 10.15625/vap.2023.0072

LANGUAGE COMPETENCY

- English: Competent user lelts 6.5 (All above 6.0)
- Finnish: Beginner Level A1.2 of Common European Framework of Reference

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Volunteer | Volunteer for Education Organization (VEO)

Teaching English for children in one of the most remote mountainous areas

Sep 2019 Mu Cang Chai, Yen Bai, Vietnam

SOFT SKILLS

Critical thinking Problem solving







Communication

